[
    {
        "question": "Decode the emojis: ğŸ»ğŸ¤—. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! âœ…",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ§ "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: bear hug. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ™Œ",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜”"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ‘»ğŸ“–. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ§ ",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! â˜‘ï¸"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: ghost story. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ‰",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. âŒ"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ¥¼ğŸ€. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! â˜‘ï¸",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ™Œ"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: lab rat. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸŠ",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜«"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸ³ğŸ“˜. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ™Œ",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ¤˜"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: cookbook. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸˆ",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ™…"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ¥šğŸš. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ¤˜",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! âœ…"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: eggshell. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ†",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ™"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ«ğŸ¥›. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! âœ…",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ™"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: chocolate milk. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ’ƒ",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜¦"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: â­ï¸ğŸŸ. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ™",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ‘Œ"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: starfish. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ¥³",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜­"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ¦€ğŸ°. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ‘Œ",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! â˜‘ï¸"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: crab cake. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ˜‡",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ‘¿"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ¬ğŸ¦·. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! â˜‘ï¸",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! â˜‘ï¸"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: sweet tooth. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ’¯",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜©"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: â›±ï¸ğŸ§™â€â™€ï¸. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! âœ…",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ˜¼"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: sandwich. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ’…",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ‘"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ—ï¸ğŸ•³ï¸. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ˜¼",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ¥°"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: keyhole. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ˜º",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜¾"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ’ªğŸª‘. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ¥°",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ‘Œ"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: armchair. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! â¤ï¸",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ’”"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ‚ğŸ. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ‘Œ",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ‘"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: birthday present. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ˜˜",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜µ"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ›ï¸ğŸ›. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ™†",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ˜"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: bedbug. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸŒ¹",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ¥€"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ¥µğŸ•. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ˜",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ™Œ"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: hot dog. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ˜™",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ¤•"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ—¿ğŸ“œâœ‚ï¸. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ™Œ",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ˜ƒ"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: rock paper scissors. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ˜",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜•"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ¦â˜€ï¸ğŸ“…. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ˜ƒ",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ§ "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: ice cream sundae. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ˜„",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜°"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ”µğŸ¤. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ§ ",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ‘"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: bluebird. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ§ ",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ˜°"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸ–ï¸ğŸŒ‰. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ‘",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ™†"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: drawbridge. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸ‘",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. ğŸ‘"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ğŸš¶ğŸ”›â˜€ï¸. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ğŸ‘",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ğŸ¤”"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: walking on sunshine. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ğŸŒ¤ï¸",
            "Nope, I didnâ€™t. â›ˆï¸"
        ]
    }
]